<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Paradigm</title>
    <link>https://johnwuelk.github.io/shane/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Paradigm</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://johnwuelk.github.io/shane/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Download original template</title>
      <link>https://johnwuelk.github.io/shane/home/downloads/download1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://johnwuelk.github.io/shane/home/downloads/download1/</guid>
      <description>A simple, nice-looking call to action box. Boxing is about respect. getting it for yourself, and taking it away from the other guy. no, this is mount everest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://johnwuelk.github.io/shane/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://johnwuelk.github.io/shane/about/</guid>
      <description>Shane Outten – Architect and Builder in the Turks and Caicos Islands Shane has over 25 years of experience in the design and construction industry in the Turks and Caicos Islands.&#xA;In short:&#xA;He is the owner of Paradigm Concepts &amp;amp; Design Architects, an architectural firm likely specializing in residential and commercial projects. He also owns IN &amp;amp; OUT Construction Ltd, a construction company that builds houses, pools, and other structures.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Construction</title>
      <link>https://johnwuelk.github.io/shane/construction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://johnwuelk.github.io/shane/construction/</guid>
      <description>IN &amp;amp; OUT Construction Ltd Our name speaks for itself, we get IN, and get OUT, doing quality work in quality time, specializing in:&#xA;Residential Projects Commercial Projects Pool Projects Building Layout Driveways Shutter Installations Boating Docks Our mission is to make your dreams become a reality by giving each individual client value for their dollar.&#xA;Contact us Today.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building in T.C.I.</title>
      <link>https://johnwuelk.github.io/shane/post/building-in-tci/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://johnwuelk.github.io/shane/post/building-in-tci/</guid>
      <description>Building in the Turks and Caicos Islands offers several attractive advantages:&#xA;Tax Haven: The Turks and Caicos Islands boast a tax-friendly environment. There&amp;rsquo;s no income, property, capital gains, or inheritance tax, making it an ideal location for those looking to maximize their investment returns.&#xA;Beautiful Location: With stunning beaches, pleasant weather year-round, and a thriving tourism industry, the islands offer a lifestyle advantage. Building here allows you to be part of a paradise destination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Limestone</title>
      <link>https://johnwuelk.github.io/shane/post/limestone-tci/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://johnwuelk.github.io/shane/post/limestone-tci/</guid>
      <description>Limestone and sandstone are both popular building materials, but with key differences:&#xA;Durability: Limestone is denser and harder, making it more resistant to scratches and wear. Sandstone is softer and can be easier to work with, but may require more care to avoid damage.&#xA;Maintenance: Limestone generally requires less upkeep due to its lower porosity. Sandstone can be more prone to staining and needs careful cleaning to avoid using harsh chemicals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://johnwuelk.github.io/shane/archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://johnwuelk.github.io/shane/archives/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://johnwuelk.github.io/shane/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://johnwuelk.github.io/shane/contact/</guid>
      <description> Feel free to contact us with your desired options: Choose your building area (sqft):&#xA;&lt; 860 ⏍ 860 - 1180 ⏍ 1600 - 2690 ⏍ 3230 ⏍ &gt; 3230 ⏍ State your price range:&#xA;– Your email:&#xA;Your name and message:&#xA;Send </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://johnwuelk.github.io/shane/home/subheader/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://johnwuelk.github.io/shane/home/subheader/</guid>
      <description>With Making Dreams Become Reality as our mantra, we offer a full range of professional services such as Architecture, Interior Design, Land Planning and Consultancy Services.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Architecture</title>
      <link>https://johnwuelk.github.io/shane/home/services/service3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://johnwuelk.github.io/shane/home/services/service3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Architecture is much more than just bricks and mortar. It&amp;rsquo;s the design and construction of buildings and other physical structures, but it also shapes the world around us in profound ways. Here&amp;rsquo;s a closer look at why architecture is so important:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Consultancy</title>
      <link>https://johnwuelk.github.io/shane/home/services/service4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://johnwuelk.github.io/shane/home/services/service4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Why Architectural Consultancy is Crucial for Building Projects&#xA;Architectural consultancy firms offer a wide range of expertise that proves invaluable throughout the building process, from a dream to a standing structure. Here&amp;rsquo;s a breakdown of why consultancy in architecture is so important:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Download HUGO template</title>
      <link>https://johnwuelk.github.io/shane/home/downloads/download2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://johnwuelk.github.io/shane/home/downloads/download2/</guid>
      <description>Another simple, nice-looking call to action box. Boxing is about respect. getting it for yourself, and taking it away from the other guy. no, this is mount everest.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Interial Design</title>
      <link>https://johnwuelk.github.io/shane/home/services/service1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://johnwuelk.github.io/shane/home/services/service1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Interior design is much more than just picking paint colors and arranging furniture. It&amp;rsquo;s the art and science of shaping a space to be both functional and aesthetically pleasing. A well-designed interior can significantly impact our lives in surprising ways. Here&amp;rsquo;s why interior design is so important:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Land Planning</title>
      <link>https://johnwuelk.github.io/shane/home/services/service2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://johnwuelk.github.io/shane/home/services/service2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Land, a finite resource, shapes how we live, work, and interact with the environment. Land planning, also known as land-use planning, is the crucial first step towards ensuring responsible and sustainable development.  In essence, it&amp;rsquo;s like a roadmap for how a piece of land will be used, balancing various needs for the benefit of the community and the environment.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
